Guide to the James M. Foster papers, 1971-1990
Foster, James M. papers, 1971-1990
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
James M. Foster papers, 1971-1990
7439
James M. Foster
12.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, subject files, reports, photographs, greeting cards, audiocassettes, accounts, and incorporation documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Foster's personal files, including correspondence, sexual audiocassettes, and records pertaining to Foster's business enterprise and various gay rights organizations. Other records concern public health issues, most notably AIDS.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
James Foster was born 19 November 1934. While living in San Francisco, he became one of the early leaders of the gay liberation movement in that city; in 1963 he helped found the Society for Individual Rights. Always active in Democratic Party local and national politics, in 1972 Foster founded the Alice B. Toklas Memorial Democratic Club (also known as the Alice B. Toklas Lesbian and Gay Democratic Club), which became particularly influential in local and national politics as the gay and lesbian constituency consolidated its power. In 1972, Foster was the first openly gay delegate to address a national convention. Professionally, Foster was a consultant dealing in fund raising issues; his business enterprise, James M. Foster and Associates, Inc., served primarily gay and human rights clients, including the Human Rights Campaign Fund. In the 1980s, Foster served as the San Francisco City Health Commissioner.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records pertain to public health issues especially pertaining to AIDS. Also included are a subject file and an AIDS file kept by Foster, and an extensive sexual audiocassette collection; also, personal correspondence, some personal files, address books, and material pertaining to Foster's business enterprise, the Democratic National Committee, the Human Rights Campaign Fund, and the Alice B. Toklas Memorial Democratic Club. Major correspondents include Dianne Feinstein, Art Agnos, David B. Goodstein, Edward M. Kennedy, Bruce Voeller, and Jerry E. Berg.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Foster, James M.; Feinstein, Dianne.; Agnos, Art.; Goodstein, David B., 1932-; Britt, Harry.; Kennedy, Edward Moore, 1932-; Voeller, Bruce; Berg, Jerry E.; Alice B. Toklas Memorial Democratic Club.; Democratic National Committee.
Subjects:
Gay men.; Gay liberation movement.; Homosexuality.; Public health.; AIDS (Disease).; Public health laws.; Health boards.; AIDS (Disease)--Prevention.; Sex and law--Homosexuality --Law and legislation.
Form and Genre Terms:
Erotica.; Pornography.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
David B. Goodstein papers, #7311
Bruce R. Voeller papers, #7307
One cubic foot of erotica and pornography was transferred to other components of the Human Sexuality Collection.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
The collection is divided into four series reflecting the basic organization used by Foster, in which the primary level of access is the folder title. His folder headings have been in all cases retained.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal Files
Box 1, folders 1-50
Box 2
Box 10, folders 1-18
Box 11, folders 49-52
Box 15, folder 36
Series II. Subject Files
General Subject files
Box 1, folders 51-63
Box 3, folders 1-64
Box 4, folders 1-5
Box 10, folders 19-119
Box 11, folders 1-57
AIDS
Box 5, folders 1-49
Box 6, folders 1-59
Box 11, folders 58-74
Box 12, folders 1-59
Box 13, folders 1-12
Health
Box 7, folders 1-17
Box 8, folders 1-12
Box 13, folders 13-57
Box 14, folders 1-54
Box 14, folders 1-54
Box 15, folders 1-55
Boxes 16-17
Series III. Audiocassettes
Box 9
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal Files
  - Correspondence
    - 1976-79 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
    - 1981-82 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1982 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
    - 1983 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
    - 1984 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
    - 1985 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1986 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 21-25)
    - 1987 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 26-29)
    - 1988 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 30-35)
    - 1989 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 36-39)
    - David B. Goodstein [eulogy] (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Pete Stark (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Stanley S. Weithorn (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence Received 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence Sent 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - James M. Foster and Associates, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 45-47)
    - Pajaro Dunes Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 48-50)
  - James Foster Personal
    - Address books, day books, appointment books, calendars, 1971-87 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, Photographs, Notes, Announcements, and Other Printed Material (Box 10, Folder 1-16)
    - Foster Notebooks (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Personal (Box 11, Folder 49-52)
    - Ireland (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Series II. Subject Files
  - General Subject Files
    - General file (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) (Box 1, Folder 53-63)
    - HRCF (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - HRCF San Jose (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HRCF Philadelphia (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - HRCF New York City (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HRCF Houston (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - HRCF Denver (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HRCF Chicago (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HRCF Washington, D.C. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - HRCF Atlanta (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - HRCF Dallas (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - HRCF Albany (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - HRCF San Antonio (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - HRCF Austin (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - HRCF Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - HRCF (Box 3, Folder 39-42)
    - Pride Center (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
    - John Tunney (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Winner/Wagner and Associates (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Southern California Prospects (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Society for Individual Rights Political Committee (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Single Taxpayers (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco Police Department (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco Board of Supervisors Candidates (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Proposals (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Penal Code Reform (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - National Gay Task Force (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Partnership Agreement (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Political Campaigns (Box 3, Folder 29-31)
    - Ron Pelosi (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Troy Perry (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bob Pritiken (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Alan Robbins (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Pride Foundation (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
    - Democratic National Committee (Box 3, Folder 43-46)
    - Queen's Bench Foundation (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Concerned Voters of California (Box 3, Folder 48-52)
    - EST and Money (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Gay Political Issues (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
    - Jim Foster Dinner (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - California Inheritance Tax (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Chuck Manatt (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby (Box 3, Folder 59-60)
    - Gay Rights Problems (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Kennedy for President (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Gay Criminal Justice System (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Publications (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Carter Presidency Campaign and 1976 Democratic Convention (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
    - Assembly Bill 489 (992) (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Assembly Bill 663 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Alice B. Toklas Democratic Club (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - A.K.C. (American Kennel Club) Papers (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Bill Bagley (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Bay Area Gay Liberation (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Bicentennial Conference (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco Board of Education (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Eugene Boyle, Rev. Fr. (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Betty Brennan (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ray Broshears (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Jerry Brown (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Willie Brown (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Vincent Buliosi (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - John Burton (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Philip Burton (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - California Catholic Conference (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - California Committee for Equal Rights (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - California Committee for Sexual Law Reform (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - California Democratic Council (CDC)
      - CDC Board of Directors (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - CDC Board of Directors (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - CDC Conventions (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - CDC Elections (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - CDC General (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - CDC Program (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - California Democratic State Central Committee (DSCC) (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - DSCC Executive Committee (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - DSCC Activities Reports (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - DSCC Reform Committee (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - California NOW, Geri Sherwood (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Canada, Gay Rights (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Jimmy Carter (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Clippings (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Coalition of Christian Citizens (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Cocktail Parties List (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Rob Cole (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Concerned Voters of California (CVC) County Coordinators (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - CVC Information Packet for County Coordinators (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Alan Cranston (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - 1976 Democratic Convention (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Dade County (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Gray Davis (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Ron Dellums (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Democratic Advisory Council (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Gay Democratic Clubs (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Democratic State Convention, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Democratic Cocktail Parties (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Mervyn Dymally (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Ed Edelman (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Election, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Employment Discrimination (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - EST (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Expenses (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Federal Legislation (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Dianne Feinstein (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - John Ferndon, District Attorney of San Francisco (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Ted Fertig (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Houston Flournoy (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Joe Freitas (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Gay Issues, Platforms, etc. (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Gay Alcoholism (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Gay Caucus (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Gay Citizens for McGovern (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Gay Coalition of Conscience (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Gay Vote (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Gay Rights, Oregon (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - David B. Goodstein (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Fred R. Harris (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Gary Hess Case (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Nate Holden (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Richard Hongisto (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - The Insider, S.I.R. (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Invitations (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Phil Isenberg (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Quentin Kopp (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Tom Kranz (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Gay Latinos (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Legislation, General (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Charles Manatt (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Marijuana Reform (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Market Street Merchants Association (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Milton Marks (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Leonard Matlovich (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - George McGovern (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Media (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Bob Mendelsohn (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Metropolitan Community Church of San Francisco (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Harvey Milk (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - John L. Molinari (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Bob Moretti (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Jack Morrison (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - George Moscone (Box 10, Folder 111-115)
    - Black Vote (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Broward County Coalition Petition (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Budget and Finance (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - California Finances (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Clergy (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Dade County Coalition (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Jack Davis (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Party Petition (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Rothenberg (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Ads (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Mailings (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Supporters and Potential Supporters (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Ordinance, Background (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Women Against Repeal (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Dade County Gay Rights Referendum, June 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - American Jewish Committee, Concerned Voters of California, Proposition 6 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Educators' Task Force (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising Letters (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Marshall Harris (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Key Precincts (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Lambda Mailing (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. William Lehman (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Leonard Matlovich (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Memos (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Miami Victory Committee (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Arthur Miller (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Rabbi Joseph Narot (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - National Gay Task Force Mailing (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - North Miami Beach (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Bill Oliver (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Phone Bank (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Precincts and Polling Areas (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Pictures (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Karoline Robinson (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Max Serchuck (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Rabbi Weberman (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Tabloid, Gay (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Politics, Issues (Box 11, Folder 35-37)
    - Advocate (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - American Jewish Congress (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Bob Basker (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Jim Foster (Box 11, Folder 41-42)
    - Steve Ross (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Support letters (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Press Releases and Stories, Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Dade County Central Committee (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Anita Bryant (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, Democratic Platform Plank Project (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Personal (Box 11, Folder 49-52)
    - Select Committee (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Charlie Gain (Box 11, Folder 54-57)
  - AIDS
    - Bleachman (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Shanti Project (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Blum Report (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    - AIDS and National Politics (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
    - Presidential Candidates Seminars (Box 5, Folder 9-12)
    - Lymphomed (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Imuthiol (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Retrovir (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Health Maintenance Programs, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - GMAC (Gay Men's Health Crisis) (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
    - AIDS Research, Care and Education, and Hostile Amendments. "The Thin Book" (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - "Fighting the War Against AIDS," California State Assembly (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - "AIDS in San Francisco," San Francisco Department of Public Health (Box 5, Folder 21-25)
    - "Report to the Committees on Armed Services of the Senate and House of Representatives on the Public Health Service Hospital, San Francisco, California" (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
    - Comprehensive AIDS Resource Emergency (CARE) Act of 1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Presidential Commission on the Human Immunodeficiency Virus Epidemic (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - County of Marin, Marin AIDS Advisory Commission (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - AIDS/HIV Experimental Treatment Directory (Box 5, Folder 31-33)
    - AIDS Surveillance Reports (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Names Project (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
    - AIDS Bulletins, Reports (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - AIDS Ambulatory Care (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
    - AIDS Legislation (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - "Patient Zero" in California Magazine (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Health Foundation (Box 5, Folder 42-43)
    - AIDS Plan (Box 5, Folder 44-46)
    - Homeless AIDS and ARCs (AIDS-Related Complexes) (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - AIDS and the California State Government (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Art Agnos (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, James M. Foster and Associates Report (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
    - In-Home Supportive Services (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - United States Labor and Human Resources Committee (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Health Data Institute (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Conference (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Caremark Advisory Committee (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Long Island (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - New York City (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Washington, D.C. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Philadelphia (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Los Angeles (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Palm Springs (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Atlanta (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Miami (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Boston (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Seattle (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Hawaii (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Northern California (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - AMBI/McKesson Conference (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - AIDS/ARC (AIDS-Related Complex) Update (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
    - Hospital Care (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
    - Joint Venture (Box 6, Folder 28-30)
    - Review of the Public Health Service's Response to AIDS (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Teacher's Curriculum Guide on AIDS (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - State AIDS Budget (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
    - Insurance (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
    - State Controller's Office (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Direct Mail (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Committee on Commissions (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - San Francisco Cares (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Newsletters (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
    - Coming Home Hospice (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Hospice of San Francisco (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Expenses (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Women's Health Issues (Box 6, Folder 46-47)
    - Veteran's Affairs (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
    - Laguna Honda Hospital and Rehabilitation Center (Box 6, Folder 50-53)
    - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center (Box 6, Folder 54-57)
    - President's Commission on AIDS (Box 6, Folder 58-59)
    - Mayor's Task Force (Box 11, Folder 58-60)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 11, Folder 61-62)
    - Press Releases and Reports, Clippings (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - California Commission (Box 11, Folder 64-67)
    - Ethnic Minorities (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Employment Issues (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - HTLV-III (Human T-cell Lymphotropic Virus type 3) (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Senate Bill 1251 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Roberti Update (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Alan Cranston (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Barbara Boxer (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Poppers (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Episcopal Church Conference (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Atlanta Conference (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Nonoxonal-9 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Legal Services (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Social Services (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - City Budget (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - State Budget (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Budget Summaries (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Forensics (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Children (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Stop AIDS Project (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - AIDS, San Francisco Reported Cases (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco Health Project (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Substance Abuse (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Robert Woods Johnson Foundation (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Extended Care Facility, Hospice (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, Pacific Telesis Foundation (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Living Memorial Foundation (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Center for Disease Control (CDC) Grant Applications (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Education (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Mayor's Lobbying Group (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Medi-Cal (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Medical and Research Communications (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Behavioral Research (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - New York Medical Foundation (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - National Council (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Bath Houses (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Legal Questions (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Budget Task Force (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - General Information (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - FYI (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Treatment Options (Box 12, Folder 34-35)
    - Mariposa Foundation (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - DAIR (Documentation of AIDS Issues and Research Foundation, Inc.) Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis) Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Multicultural Inquiry and Research on AIDS (MIRA) Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Funding (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Agnos/Conference of Mayors (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Substance Abuse (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Needle Exchange (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Immigration Concerns (Box 12, Folder 44-45)
    - Sixth International Conference on AIDS (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Seventh International Conference on AIDS (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Surveillance Reports (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Kennedy-Hatch Care Bill, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - AIDS Minorities (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - Hispanic Minority (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Black Minority (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Asian Minority (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Discrimination (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Pediatrics (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Insurance/Payment (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Case Management (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Housing (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Home Care (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - SNFS/Nursing Homes (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Early Intervention (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Community and Hospital Care Report (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Costs of Out of Hospital Programs (report) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Ambulatory Care (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco General Hospital (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Planning (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Who Pays?" (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - AZT (Retrovir) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - HIV Task Force 1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - HIV Task Force 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - HIV Task Force Report (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Health
    - Long Term Health Care (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Lesbian and Gay Health Services (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
    - Travel (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Needle Exchange Program (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - CFIDS (Chronic Fatigue and Immune Dysfunction Syndrome) Chronicle (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco City Heath Commission (Box 7, Folder 8-12)
    - Drugs (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco General Hospital Medical Center Institution Master Plan (Box 7, Folder 15-17)
    - Juvenile Victims of Sexual Abuse (Box 8, Folder 1-12)
    - Services for the Elderly (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Susan Lowe, Safeway (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - National Society of Fundraisers (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Domestic Partners Legislation (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco, Gay Demographics (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - CSAS (Community Substance Abuse Services) and Drug Abuse (Box 13, Folder 18-22)
    - Bilingual Services/Problems (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Department of Public Health (DPH)/Laguna Honda Hospital (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Commissioner James Foster (Box 13, Folder 25-26)
    - Sacramento County (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Financial Statements (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Expense Reports (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Vendoes-Voter Contact (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Accounts Receivable, SFAF (San Francisco AIDS Foundation) (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Hospice Proposal, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Department of Public Health (DPH) Budget (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Hospices (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Substance Abuse/BAART (Bay Area Addition Research and Treatment) (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Tenderloin Drop-In Clinic (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Mental Health/Reform Act (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Department of Public Health (DPH)/Emergency Medical Services (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Health Program Coordinators (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Substance Abuse - 18th Street (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Mayor's Health Task force (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Joint Conference Committee Community Health (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Shanti Project (AIDS Support Services) (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - MIA (Medically Indigent Adults) Program (Box 13, Folder 45)